{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947250864183","data":{"timestamp":" 947250864183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947250868834","data":{"timestamp":" 947250868834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947250872746","data":{"timestamp":" 947250872746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947250881295","data":{"timestamp":" 947250881295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947250885666","data":{"timestamp":" 947250885666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947250889111","data":{"timestamp":" 947250889111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947250895065","data":{"timestamp":" 947250895065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947250951246","data":{"timestamp":" 947250951246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947250963779","data":{"timestamp":" 947250963779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947250968001","data":{"timestamp":" 947250968001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947250972365","data":{"timestamp":" 947250972365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947250975949","data":{"timestamp":" 947250975949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947250985718","data":{"timestamp":" 947250985718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947250990364","data":{"timestamp":" 947250990364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251000960","data":{"timestamp":" 947251000960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251004346","data":{"timestamp":" 947251004346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251008900","data":{"timestamp":" 947251008900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251015205","data":{"timestamp":" 947251015205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251022458","data":{"timestamp":" 947251022458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251043250","data":{"timestamp":" 947251043250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251048663","data":{"timestamp":" 947251048663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251053804","data":{"timestamp":" 947251053804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251063295","data":{"timestamp":" 947251063295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251068854","data":{"timestamp":" 947251068854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251074632","data":{"timestamp":" 947251074627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" c57bd90d-f749-4302-950a-97743fd37241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251129352","data":{"timestamp":" 947251129352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251131524","data":{"timestamp":" 947251131523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251133684","data":{"timestamp":" 947251133684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251136921","data":{"timestamp":" 947251136920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251139196","data":{"timestamp":" 947251139195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251141437","data":{"timestamp":" 947251141435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251144295","data":{"timestamp":" 947251144294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251146524","data":{"timestamp":" 947251146524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251148740","data":{"timestamp":" 947251148739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251152032","data":{"timestamp":" 947251152032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251154173","data":{"timestamp":" 947251154172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251156283","data":{"timestamp":" 947251156282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251159292","data":{"timestamp":" 947251159291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251161531","data":{"timestamp":" 947251161530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251163757","data":{"timestamp":" 947251163756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251166850","data":{"timestamp":" 947251166849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251169190","data":{"timestamp":" 947251169190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251171524","data":{"timestamp":" 947251171523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251174596","data":{"timestamp":" 947251174595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251176774","data":{"timestamp":" 947251176773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251178940","data":{"timestamp":" 947251178940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251182072","data":{"timestamp":" 947251182071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251184266","data":{"timestamp":" 947251184265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251186479","data":{"timestamp":" 947251186478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251189686","data":{"timestamp":" 947251189685"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251192131","data":{"timestamp":" 947251192130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251194560","data":{"timestamp":" 947251194558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251197745","data":{"timestamp":" 947251197745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251200031","data":{"timestamp":" 947251200030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251202288","data":{"timestamp":" 947251202287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251205303","data":{"timestamp":" 947251205302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251207525","data":{"timestamp":" 947251207524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251209720","data":{"timestamp":" 947251209719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251212721","data":{"timestamp":" 947251212720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251215101","data":{"timestamp":" 947251215100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251217511","data":{"timestamp":" 947251217511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251220638","data":{"timestamp":" 947251220638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251223037","data":{"timestamp":" 947251223036"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251225433","data":{"timestamp":" 947251225432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251228471","data":{"timestamp":" 947251228470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251230752","data":{"timestamp":" 947251230751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251233062","data":{"timestamp":" 947251233061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251236336","data":{"timestamp":" 947251236335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251238589","data":{"timestamp":" 947251238588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251240881","data":{"timestamp":" 947251240880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251244221","data":{"timestamp":" 947251244221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251246702","data":{"timestamp":" 947251246701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251249156","data":{"timestamp":" 947251249155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251252056","data":{"timestamp":" 947251252055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251254246","data":{"timestamp":" 947251254245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251256465","data":{"timestamp":" 947251256465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251259921","data":{"timestamp":" 947251259920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251262272","data":{"timestamp":" 947251262272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251264594","data":{"timestamp":" 947251264593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251267762","data":{"timestamp":" 947251267761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251270021","data":{"timestamp":" 947251270021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251272278","data":{"timestamp":" 947251272277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251275320","data":{"timestamp":" 947251275319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251277455","data":{"timestamp":" 947251277455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251279577","data":{"timestamp":" 947251279577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251282713","data":{"timestamp":" 947251282713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251284939","data":{"timestamp":" 947251284938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251287226","data":{"timestamp":" 947251287226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251290479","data":{"timestamp":" 947251290478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251292695","data":{"timestamp":" 947251292694"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251294930","data":{"timestamp":" 947251294930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251298209","data":{"timestamp":" 947251298208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251300516","data":{"timestamp":" 947251300516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251302854","data":{"timestamp":" 947251302853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251306014","data":{"timestamp":" 947251306013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251308347","data":{"timestamp":" 947251308346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251310727","data":{"timestamp":" 947251310726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251314147","data":{"timestamp":" 947251314146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251314245","data":{"timestamp":" 947251314245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 50be7a84-7edd-4348-881f-4759eb5f4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251386202","data":{"timestamp":" 947251386201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251386589","data":{"timestamp":" 947251386589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251387089","data":{"timestamp":" 947251387088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251387445","data":{"timestamp":" 947251387444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251387859","data":{"timestamp":" 947251387858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251388344","data":{"timestamp":" 947251388344"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251388569","data":{"timestamp":" 947251388569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251391696","data":{"timestamp":" 947251391695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251391730","data":{"timestamp":" 947251391730"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251392444","data":{"timestamp":" 947251392444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251392838","data":{"timestamp":" 947251392838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251393131","data":{"timestamp":" 947251393131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251393335","data":{"timestamp":" 947251393335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251393528","data":{"timestamp":" 947251393528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251393842","data":{"timestamp":" 947251393842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251394066","data":{"timestamp":" 947251394066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251397201","data":{"timestamp":" 947251397201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251397604","data":{"timestamp":" 947251397603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251400111","data":{"timestamp":" 947251400110"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251400313","data":{"timestamp":" 947251400313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251400516","data":{"timestamp":" 947251400516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251403947","data":{"timestamp":" 947251403947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251407621","data":{"timestamp":" 947251407621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251408644","data":{"timestamp":" 947251408644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251411272","data":{"timestamp":" 947251411271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251411646","data":{"timestamp":" 947251411646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251412128","data":{"timestamp":" 947251412128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251412471","data":{"timestamp":" 947251412471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251412874","data":{"timestamp":" 947251412874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251413348","data":{"timestamp":" 947251413348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251413571","data":{"timestamp":" 947251413571"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251416737","data":{"timestamp":" 947251416737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251416772","data":{"timestamp":" 947251416772"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251417486","data":{"timestamp":" 947251417486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251417880","data":{"timestamp":" 947251417879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251418173","data":{"timestamp":" 947251418173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251418375","data":{"timestamp":" 947251418375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251418569","data":{"timestamp":" 947251418569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251418884","data":{"timestamp":" 947251418884"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251419108","data":{"timestamp":" 947251419108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251421810","data":{"timestamp":" 947251421809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251421936","data":{"timestamp":" 947251421936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" 30e64034-fc8a-47c9-88d3-d5129655bff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251478645","data":{"timestamp":" 947251478644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vipepeo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPEPEO"," userResponse":" VIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251482017","data":{"timestamp":" 947251482017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vipepeo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPEPEO"," userResponse":" VIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251483617","data":{"timestamp":" 947251483616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vikapu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKAPU"," userResponse":" VIKAPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251486398","data":{"timestamp":" 947251486397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vikapu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKAPU"," userResponse":" VIKAPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251487996","data":{"timestamp":" 947251487995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251491238","data":{"timestamp":" 947251491237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251492876","data":{"timestamp":" 947251492875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251495740","data":{"timestamp":" 947251495740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251497391","data":{"timestamp":" 947251497390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251500842","data":{"timestamp":" 947251500842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" START_VITUMBUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251502935","data":{"timestamp":" 947251502935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251504539","data":{"timestamp":" 947251504538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vijiti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIJITI"," userResponse":" VIJITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251508025","data":{"timestamp":" 947251508024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vijiti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIJITI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251509612","data":{"timestamp":" 947251509611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251512473","data":{"timestamp":" 947251512472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251514074","data":{"timestamp":" 947251514073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" visu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VISU"," userResponse":" VISU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251516670","data":{"timestamp":" 947251516670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" visu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VISU"," userResponse":" VISU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251518265","data":{"timestamp":" 947251518264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251521166","data":{"timestamp":" 947251521166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251523192","data":{"timestamp":" 947251523191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" vidogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251523311","data":{"timestamp":" 947251523311"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b163c380-08d5-4898-bf3c-a3b94586a312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251537922","data":{"timestamp":" 947251537921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vipepeo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPEPEO"," userResponse":" VIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251545887","data":{"timestamp":" 947251545887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vipepeo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPEPEO"," userResponse":" VIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251547517","data":{"timestamp":" 947251547516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vikapu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKAPU"," userResponse":" VIKAPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251550046","data":{"timestamp":" 947251550045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vikapu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKAPU"," userResponse":" VIKAPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251551653","data":{"timestamp":" 947251551653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251558245","data":{"timestamp":" 947251558244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251559859","data":{"timestamp":" 947251559858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251562535","data":{"timestamp":" 947251562535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251564166","data":{"timestamp":" 947251564166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251569006","data":{"timestamp":" 947251569006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" START_VITUMBUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251571815","data":{"timestamp":" 947251571814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251573390","data":{"timestamp":" 947251573389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vijiti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIJITI"," userResponse":" VIJITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251577104","data":{"timestamp":" 947251577104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vijiti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIJITI"," userResponse":" VIJITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251578711","data":{"timestamp":" 947251578710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251587625","data":{"timestamp":" 947251587625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251589227","data":{"timestamp":" 947251589227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" visu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VISU"," userResponse":" VISU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251592192","data":{"timestamp":" 947251592191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" visu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VISU"," userResponse":" VISU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251593808","data":{"timestamp":" 947251593807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251596871","data":{"timestamp":" 947251596871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251598880","data":{"timestamp":" 947251598880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" vidogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251598964","data":{"timestamp":" 947251598964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251622907","data":{"timestamp":" 947251622907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" f350fbbb-943c-41df-b767-c0aba9a23559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" vidogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251647161","data":{"timestamp":" 947251647161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b573f85c-51cc-48cc-9e0e-d27227efc29f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_f-g-v"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251653293","data":{"timestamp":" 947251653293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b573f85c-51cc-48cc-9e0e-d27227efc29f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-u"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251661113","data":{"timestamp":" 947251661113"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b573f85c-51cc-48cc-9e0e-d27227efc29f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_w-v-u"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251668992","data":{"timestamp":" 947251668992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b573f85c-51cc-48cc-9e0e-d27227efc29f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-o-b"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251673635","data":{"timestamp":" 947251673635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b573f85c-51cc-48cc-9e0e-d27227efc29f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-t-y"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251679011","data":{"timestamp":" 947251679010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b573f85c-51cc-48cc-9e0e-d27227efc29f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-t-y"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251687862","data":{"timestamp":" 947251687861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b573f85c-51cc-48cc-9e0e-d27227efc29f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-t-y"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251698176","data":{"timestamp":" 947251698176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b573f85c-51cc-48cc-9e0e-d27227efc29f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_j-u-v"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251787806","data":{"timestamp":" 947251787806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b573f85c-51cc-48cc-9e0e-d27227efc29f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_l-y-v"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251798701","data":{"timestamp":" 947251798701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b573f85c-51cc-48cc-9e0e-d27227efc29f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_i-ch-v"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251806615","data":{"timestamp":" 947251806615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b573f85c-51cc-48cc-9e0e-d27227efc29f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_a-t-v"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251821412","data":{"timestamp":" 947251821412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b573f85c-51cc-48cc-9e0e-d27227efc29f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_f-k-v"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947251827191","data":{"timestamp":" 947251827190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_161402"," gameId":" b573f85c-51cc-48cc-9e0e-d27227efc29f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_v_f-k-v"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}